The kettle and the idol
Now, the second.
I'm making it.
Textile.
It's a tekito.
This is not a tekito that makes a mess,
Yes, it is.
This is,
I made it crumpled, but the letters.
I don't know how to say it. It's just a kind of texturedness that was in the right place at the right time,
Basically, I'm not very good at it,
I don't know what to say.
I wonder why. I certainly have that image.
There are many things that I can do as well as anyone else to some extent,
So, I am the right person for the right job,
I think it depends on the time,
I can still get by?
That's what I mean.
I see.
How is that? I don't know.
It seems like something that could be done in Mie Prefecture.
Yes, it is.
Yes, there is.
That's right.
I was actually told that, and I was like, "I can do that much.
That's right. Basically, it is not too much to say that it is impossible.
Ah.
I can get through quite a few of them,
By the way, is there anything in your life that has been a little tough for you?
Yes, I have.
Surprisingly, I don't have any,
I don't have any.
Yes, I have. But on the other hand, it is often a disadvantage,
How is it a disadvantage?
It's great to have something that is well drawn out, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
So even if you could keep everything constant, it would still be a problem,
That is a bit of a problem for me,
I'm not going to let anyone beat me in this.
So you're doing it buried in the average.
But you are tall and have impressive ears,
But with your height and impressive ears, you must be one of the best in the office, right?
I am often told that I have long arms and legs,
I hope I'm better than others in those areas.
Yes, that's right.
Ears and arms and legs.
It's a genetic trait.
That's right.
Like the volume of Mr. Mita's food,
I guess that means there is a big pull?
Yes, indeed.
But I love eating out,
I go to all kinds of cafes and yakiniku restaurants by myself.
Oh, really? Really? So you are core active.
That's right. I usually go to yakiniku alone, pizza alone, and Italian restaurants alone,
Italian food alone? Yes.
I also go to all-you-can-eat restaurants.
You don't eat all you can eat by yourself?
Yes, I do. There are yakiniku restaurants.
All-you-can-eat yakiniku by yourself.
Yes, I do. I go there.
Wow, that's amazing.
But you certainly know what you are getting out of it.
Yes, I do.
While searching for it. I am in the process of searching for the part of myself that I don't know the most yet.
I am still searching for something that I have a firm grasp on.
Yes, I have. I am finding something to hold on to.
I understand.
I was in high school about 5 times a week.
I was doing this show about 5 times a week,
Bake-chan
Mr. Fuji
Mr. Gopa
Mr. Kuribon
and Yo-san.
Thank you very much.
I hope you are getting to know me a little better.
Please wait for the next installment!